Loudbone! Flare Song!
Wanival! Aqua Cutter!
That’s actually kinda hitting...
...the feels!
Ready, set, and... GO! READY! GO!
We’re in top-notch mode
You’re not alone, you know?
Put our palms together, raise them high, and let our lights unite
pOCket Monsters
Wonder Voyage
In rain, gales, or even blizzards
We can laugh together as friends
All of the gaps in the Index
let’s fill them in bit by bit
If you’re trying to be someone else
Don’t think like that
You’re fine just as you are
Don’t lose yourself
Recollect on what’s in your pocket
This is what makes us strong
A heartfelt bond that will never fade
Ready, set, and...
GO! READY! GO!
We’re in top-notch mode
You’re not alone, you know?
Let’s fly, higher and higher!
It’s fine to make mistakes
just rest your wings
When you’ve caught your breath
you can fly off once more!
Come along with us, oh-oh
Voltteccers
Pass the endlessly turning seasons,
and venture into brand-new skies
Crazy Feels! This Is a Pokémon Contest, Dearie!!
Awesome as usual, Dot!
Such a pretty photo!
Maybe that’s the magic of
the sunset at work...
It just kinda hit the feels for me.
The feels?
Masquernya’s move just happened to
add on to the others!
I name it the Feels Special!
Who said you get to name it?
It’s a good name.
The Feels Special!
What’s this “feels” stuff?!
Roy, you battled with Mr. Colza
and Mr. Hassaku at Orange Academy, right?
I was thinking about that, too!
Fire and Ice moves
collided with each other...
...and everyone there was captivated.
I’d like it if more people
got to see ours, too.
Then I’ve got a good idea!
A Pokémon Contest!
That could be great!
Oh yeah,
that’s one way to do it!
We can show everyone
the Feels Special!
What, they don’t even battle?
Huh... Cuteness, Beauty, Coolness...
A tournament where you compete in those categories?
We can work together
and put on a lovely show.
Looks like they want to join in, too.
But ordinarily, only one trainer
gives commands to the Pokémon in a contest.
So the three pairs of us can’t enter?
But without Loudbone, Wanival, and Masquernya
all together, we can’t do the Feels Special!
Oh, it says that one representative
can bring in other people’s Pokémon.
Let’s do that, then!
Rock, paper, scissors...
...shoot!
Whoa, I won...
Then you’re our rep, Liko.
Loudbone, make sure
you listen closely to what Liko says!
You too, Wanival!
Here’s to being a team!
And her stage costume?
Leave that to me.
Okay, you’re entered!
What, already?!
I haven’t had time to take all this in...
Don’t worry.
You’ve got a great coach at your side!
A coach?
Leave it to Navi, dearie!
“Dearie”?!
What, you an expert?
Saw a vid about it yesterday.
Only seen a vid?!
Let’s show off what makes
each of us special!
Let’s work together
and do our best!
Now, hustle time, dearie!
Seriously, what is that character
you’re playing?
Start the music!
Loudbone!
Flare Song, please!
Listen to what Liko says!
Wanival! Aqua Cutter!
Yeah!
Sorry, Masquernya.
Just hold on a bit right now!
Wanival, you fired those late!
Stop! Stop, dearie!
The Feels Special
isn’t coming together too well...
Giving commands to Pokémon that
aren’t your partners is tough, eh?
Loudbone and Wanival aren’t used to
working together with Liko, either...
Coach. Got any good ideas?
Well, if you put me on the spot...
When you’re lost,
watch a vid, dearie!
Coach...
A vid...?
That’s it!
When Loudbone fires his Flare Song,
you add your Aqua Cutter to it, Wanival.
That’ll make it so when they collide,
it’ll spread out beautifully.
Loudbone! Flare Song!
Wanival! Aqua Cutter!
Masquernya! Magical Leaf!
Huh?!
Masquernya...
Sorry! I’m not mad!
How about we take a little break?
Sorry, Masquernya.
But let’s give practice our all!
One more try after the break!
That’s cool!
What a crowd.
And they’re all here
for the Pokémon Contest, aren’t they?
Going in person is just
extra good, y’know?
Somethin’ smells good!
Let’s go, Yamirami!
Well, Ult’s being led by his appetite...
So how about we kick back and enjoy ourselves, too?
Sounds like the right idea.
We got the Feels Special all sharpened up
and looking real good, too.
You’re right.
Okay, let’s go!
Those Pikachu must be contestants, too!
They’re the famous Cutie Pikapika!
Apparently they’re contest regulars.
Their costumes are really detailed, too.
They’ve got their routine down to a tee,
and they’re all so cute!
Let’s hurry up and go, dearie!
Huh...? Hey, wait for me!
So cute!
Not bad, dearie, but what I seek is
an unprecedented, exciting performance.
You’ve still quite a ways to go before you might
perhaps impress my esteemed Bunyatto and me, dearie.
The real live Yuzuko’s here!
She’s just like the vids, dearie!
So it was her rubbing off on you.
Tyltalis!
Sing, followed by Cotton Guard!
Why, it’s practically snowing!
What a fantastical atmosphere!
Amamaiko! Fawn!
Rokon! Flamethrower!
The snowscape suddenly
turns into a shining starry sky!
Finish it up! Triple Axel!
A performance interweaving
fire and fluff!
The Coolness, the Beauty, the Cuteness!
I expect high scores in each category!
That was Mr. Snow J. Powder, folks!
Thank you, everyone!
That was incredible... Beautiful...
Who knew Pokémon moves
could manage performances like that?
Tyltalis’s song was so nice!
Gave me an airy feeling in my heart...
And I... have to get up
on the same stage they did, right?
Liko?
I just... suddenly got all worried.
So Liko gets worried too...
Huh? I mean...
You’re level-headed and reliable, so I thought
you were the kinda person who could do anything.
Definitely not.
Then thank goodness Navi’s here!
Huh?
‘Cause nothing scares Navi!
The two of us’d be
the strongest duo around, right?
Navi...
Don’t worry.
I know you can do it, Liko!
You’ve practiced so much, after all.
And Loudbone and the others
will do all they can to help!
Here’s your costume for today.
Thank you.
I’ll try my best!
If anyone goes badmouthing Liko,
I’ll get Ult to knock ‘em out!
Not happenin’.
Huh?
Ult said something sensible for once...
Ms. Liko, please be ready
and standing by!
Right!
Let’s all make this
into one incredible show!
pOCket Monsters
Wonder Voyage
The next team to participate will be
Meow-Meow-Liko-Liko and Her Friends!
Dot...
Metamon, over here.
Let’s go!
Loudbone! Flamethrower!
Such intensity!
Loudbone’s fire basks the stage in blazing color!
Wanival! Wave Tackle!
Air Cutter!
How beautiful!
Combo moves from Loudbone and Wanival
create a fantasy realm of fire, water, and wind!
You’re both doing incredible!
Good work, Wanival!
Not a hitch so far!
Next up...
Masquernya! Trick Flower!
Huh?! Where are you going?!
What’s this?!
An unexpected exit from Masquernya?!
Oho...
Did you spot that,
my esteemed Bunyatto?
That was no mere accident.
The jealousy and fussiness
of the Pokémon known as Masquernya...
She is making a deliberate
display of them!
Loudbone!
A Flare Song melody, please!
Wanival!
A big dance and Aqua Cutter!
Give it all you’ve got, Loudbone!
Wanival! Show them
your signature dance moves!
Masquernya?
With Masquernya’s exit, the performance continues
with only Loudbone and Wanival!
Metamon’s so cute!
Bravo. An exhibition of Masquernya’s conscience,
having divested herself of her jealous side...
I-Is that what that was?
Of course...
The way you moved back then...
You weren’t just playing around.
Metamon wanted to join in
on the Feels Special too, didn’t it?
I’m sorry I took so long to realize!
Let’s push this show to its peak!
You too, Metamon!
A-Astoundingly, a Metamon makes
an unregistered appearance! This is unheard of!
Exceedingly interesting, dearie.
Huh?
A surprise that betrays expectations.
Now that is the true appeal
of a live performance!
How beautiful! A carnival comprised
of fire and water, of flowers and smiles!
Err... After careful review...
Team “Meow-Meow-Liko-Liko and Her Friends”
is disqualified for a breach of regulations.
Huh?!
She did use a Pokémon
that hadn’t been entered, after all...
But it was cute so who cares?!
It was one incredible show!
Rules are rules, dearies.
However...
It shook my heart, dearies.
The purity of passion in its desire
to take the stage alongside its friends...
And the impromptu teamwork
they reciprocated with...
Bravo, dearies.
As such... We will award you
the Judge’s Special Prize, dearies.
Huh?
Did we even have a prize like that?!
We do now, dearie.
Congrats, dearie.
Th-Thank you very much!
Huh?
Ah!
Congrats, dearie.
Ahh! That was so much fun!
Mmm, and I got to eat a ton of tasty stuff!
Contest stalls ain’t nothin’ to scoff at!
Sheesh, you haven’t stopped eating
since we got here, Ult!
Anyway, Liko’s show is the important thing!
And it hit the feels like crazy!
Though it ended up full of surprises.
Yeah. That’s why it hit so many feels.
Still don’t get it.
It wasn’t a show that’ll go down in the record books,
but it’ll stick in peoples’ memories, don’t you think?
Thanks to Navi’s coaching, dearie!
You’re right about that.
Thanks, Navi.
And thanks for the cute costume, Dot!
I got to take plenty more good photos.
I had a great time, too.
Metamon! Aren’t you glad
Masquernya invited you on stage?
And you, Masquernya... Thanks for all the effort
you put in to make it a lovely show!
Wanival, you really
glitzed it up again today!
Your song echoed across that huge stage!
Your singing was so cool, Loudbone!
Thanks to all your help,
it turned out to be one incredible Pokémon Contest!
Events always leave you feeling accomplished,
but a little sad they’re over, don’t they?
Yeah...
The night’s first star!
Now that...
...hits the feels!
I keep tellin’ ya
I still don’t get it!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Friede here!
It’s time to Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie!
Today’s topic is Pikachu!
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Pikachu
Classification
Type
Height
Weight
Ability
Mouse Pokémon
Electric
Static
A famous face
who needs no introduction.
So then, do you know where you should look
to tell males and females apart?
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
See the answer after the commercials!
Oh! One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
Gonna give my motivation button a little tap!
The power of hard work is amazing!
(Ahem!)
But if I slack off I might end up devolving...
Well, that’s no good!
But now you mention it...
I know button mashing won’t help at all
So stop shaking this maiden’s heart already
(Stop it!)
Getting attached, but then they turn away
When things just don’t go the way that you want...
Isn’t it so fun? Doesn’t it make your heart race?
Doesn’t it make you all excited?
When I feel a spark...
I’ll catch it in a Cutesy Capsule
Face to face with the dream I’ve always imagined...
I’ve got electric jolts running through me!
I’m so lovey-dovey I can’t even move!
When I know change is still inside of me...
I’ll catch it in a Cutesy Capsule
then we can be together forever
We’ll conquer any obstacle!
I know our future will shine!
So let’s be friends!
Pick up you! I want you! Hit chu straight in the heart!
Pick up you! I want you! We’re right at the peak of our adven-chu!!
Oh! One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
One toss makes a red-white-spinny-shaky
Cutesy Capsule
One click makes a rolly-wobbly-all-aflutter
onlooking Street
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Time to announce
the correct answer!
The answer is...
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
Their tails
Their ears
Their eyelashes
A: Their tails!
Their tails
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Unlike males, the tails of females
are heart-shaped.
Mega-Study With Instructor Starmie
Oh.
That reminds me, when Pikachu gather,
electricity builds up, and thunder—
Next episode
Hey, Liko, have you heard of
the Mototokage Race?
Every year, they race a full lap
around Paldea! It’s awesome!
And everyone rides a Mototokage?
Yeah! The teams put these
flashy outfits on them, so it’s fun to watch!
Next episode
Sorta like those?
Yeah, exactly!
That Mototokage looks strong;
it even has a crest!
Next episode
And that one’s cool too!
It’s glowing!
And so, to be continued
next time on Pocket Monsters!
Koraidon & Miraidon! The Great Paldea Race!!
Are those really Mototokage...?